zocku.com 2009-11-07

# Zocku | Social Network Maker - Create social networking websites, blogs, forum & more

## Zocku Privacy Policy

Date of Last Revision: February 5, 2009

This privacy policy governs our collection, storage and use of personal data when you register and create a social network ("Network") using the Zocku website at [zocku.com](http://www.zocku.com/ "zocku") (the " **Website** "). It provides you with details about the personal data we collect from you and users of your Network, how we use that personal data and your and their rights to control our use of personal data. Please read this privacy policy carefully – by visiting this Website and creating and/or using any Network (the " **Services** "), you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy in its entirety. If you do not agree to this privacy policy in its entirety, you must not use the Services. 

This privacy policy was last updated on February 5, 2009. Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates to this privacy policy. 

### Who we are

Zocku.com is a trading name of SocialGO Limited, a company registered in England and Wales (registration number 04463402) and whose registered office is at 7 Pilgrim Street, London EC4V 6LB. We respect the right that you and users of your Network have to privacy and will only process personal data you or they provide to us in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and other applicable privacy laws. 

If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use personal data, or if you have any other privacy-related questions, please e-mail us at: [support@zocku.com](mailto:support@zocku.com "Mail Zocku"). 

### An important note about children

We do not and will not knowingly collect information from any person under the age of 18. You must not create or attempt to create any Network that allows or encourages use or registration by any person under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you may not register with any Network or use any of the Services. 

### The personal data we collect

When you or users of your network access and browse the Services (including when you create a Network or you or your users submit personal data to us through data entry fields on the Services), we may collect the following information: 

  1. the name of you and your users; 
  2. the age, date of birth and sex of you and your users; 
  3. the postal address of you and your users; 
  4. phone and e-mail details of you and your users; 
  5. employment details of you and your users (these are optional); 
  6. payment details of you and your users if you or they choose to subscribe to or otherwise access paid-for content; and 
  7. any other personal data that you or your users choose to upload to or post on the Services, including blogs, photographs, messages, hobbies and interests and other personal details. 

In addition, we may collect anonymised details about visitors to our Services for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes. However, no single individual will be identifiable from the anonymised details that we collect for these purposes. 

### How we may store and use information

We (or third party data processors acting on our behalf) may collect, store and use personal data listed above relating to you and your users for the following purposes: 

  1. to make the Services available to you and to provide you and your users with content which is tailored to your or their individual tastes; 
  2. to complete any purchases you or your users make through the Services and to provide services that you or they request; 
  3. to further develop and improve the Services; 
  4. to maintain and support any customer account that you have with us; 
  5. to include (or to permit the inclusion of) advertising within the Services of our own and third party products, services and promotions that we or they think may interest you; 
  6. where we have obtained consent from you or your users, to contact you or them (as applicable) with products, services and promotions (including by SMS and e-mail) which we think may interest you or them; and 
  7. where we have obtained consent from you or your users, to disclose your or their (as applicable) personal data to carefully chosen third parties so that they may contact you or them with products, services and promotions (including by SMS and e-mail) which they think may interest you or them. 

Other than as set out in this privacy policy, we will not disclose, sell or rent personal data about you or your users to any third party unless you have consented to this. If you do consent but later change your mind, you may contact us and we will cease any such activity. 

However, if a third party acquires all (or substantially all) of our business and/or assets, we may disclose personal data about you and your users to that third party in connection with the acquisition. 

We may also disclose personal data about you and your users where we are required to do so by applicable law, by order of a court, by a governmental body or by a law enforcement agency. We may also disclose personal data about you and your users in the context of investigating or reporting any issue arising in connection with activity by you or them or content supplied or purporting to be supplied by you or them, to you or them or on your or their behalf that we reasonably believe could be unlawful or otherwise in breach of our terms of service. 

### International transfers

We may transfer personal data that we collect from you and your users to our group companies and other third parties located in countries that are outside of the European Economic Area where necessary to exercise, or in connection with, the uses of your data described above. Please be aware that countries which are outside the European Economic Area may not offer the same level of data protection as the United Kingdom, although our collection, storage and use of your personal data will continue to be governed by this privacy policy. 

### Cookies

This website uses cookies to collect information about you and your users. Cookies are small data files which are placed on your computer by this website and which collect certain personal data about you and your users. This enables us to tailor our service offering (including the website) to provide you and your users with products and services which are more relevant to your and their individual tastes. However, you and your users may change your website browser settings to reject cookies, although please note that if you or they do this it may impair the functionality of the Services. As each website browser is different, please visit your browser's "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

### Security

Whilst we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal data that you and your users provide to us, no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed secure. Consequently, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any personal data that you or they transfer over the Internet to us. 

### Your rights

You have the following rights: 

  1. the right to ask us to provide you with copies of personal data that we hold about you at any time, subject to a fee specified by law (currently £10); 
  2. the right to ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal data that we hold about you free of charge; and 
  3. the right to opt out of any marketing communications that we may send you. 

Users of any Network you create also have the right to contact us for any of the above purposes in connection with our use of their personal data. If you or they wish to exercise any of the above rights, please e-mail us at the address specified above. 

### Third party sites

This privacy policy applies to any personal data that we collect about you or users of any Network that you create and host on the Services. However, this website also contains links to other third party websites and Networks over which we have no control. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the personal data that we collect through the Services and we cannot be responsible for personal data that third party website operators or third party Network owners may collect, store and use through their independent websites and Networks. You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully. If you are a user of a Network, you should first read the privacy policy of the Network to which you have subscribed and contact the operator of that Network with any questions or concerns before contacting us.
